Guide to the St. Thomas More Editorial Project, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Library. St. Thomas More Editorial Project, 1958-1994; Accession 1997-A-025
  - Editorial committee meeting; February 3, 1960 and March 3 and 8, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Editorial committee meeting; August 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Editorial committee; October 22, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Editorial committee; January 24, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Editorial committee; September 18, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Editorial committee meeting; December 9, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Editorial committee; January 11, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Editorial committee; April 19, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Editorial committee; June 19, July 11, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Editorial committee; October 2, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Editorial committee; November 5, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Editorial committee confutation; December 7, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Editorial committee; January 21, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Editorial committee; January 16, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Editorial committee; November 1, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Editorial committee; June 1, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Eques Auratus, Origin of Term, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Erasmus, Undated (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Erasmus, more correspondence; Allen, Rogers, Nichols, Undated (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Expenses; March-July 1965 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Florilegia, 15th century and early 16th century, Undated (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Flynn, MP (1938), Englishmen in Rome During the Renaissance, March 19, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Folger,Petrarch celebrations, April 6-13, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Gallup, report on Gibson's bibliography, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Forward to Gibson and estimate sheet, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Gibson, free copy lists, Undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Gibson, Moreana items not at Yale as of October 10, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Gibson presentation, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Smith, Gibson; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Glossary, Burchfield opinion, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Glossary, list of abbreviations, Undated (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Grants, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Greek abbreviations, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Grynaeus, Novus Orbis, Undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Dialogue of Comfort, October 22, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Harvey, On More, Undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Haupt, translation report; thesis principles, etc..., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Haupt, Treatise on the Passion, Undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Henry VIII, Yale copy of Assertio (German translation), Undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Hexter, Machiavelli and More article, stato generoso, September 1, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Hills, A.C., thesis or dialogues, Undated (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Huntington lists of microfilms, 1938-1942, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - IBM members, used for billings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Inventory, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Jesus College, Oxford, Undated (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Kitt Hath Lost Her Key, Undated (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Legal Quarter (London, 1563), map, July 7, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - List of volumes and publications schedule, May 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Longstaff collection, catalogue; Loyola, L.A., Undated (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Loyola, More collection, Undated (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Lucian, necromantia, Rastell, Shirburn copy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Lusardi, Textual preface to dissertation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Luther, Undated (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Project mailing list, October 8, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Marc'hadour, Encyclopedia Brittanica, article on More, March 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Marc'hadour, report on Richard 3 MS, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Marymount College, Pellisier Library, More collection, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Medical Library, 1960, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Microfilms, project holdings to February 15, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Modern language association, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Micro Methods Ltd., Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Missals, Haupt, Sr. Scholastica, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - MLA, newsletter, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - MLA, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - MLA, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - MLA, N.Y.C., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - MLA, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - MLA, Chicago, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - MLA, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - MLA, Chicago, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - MLA, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - MLA, Chicago, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - MLA, Philadelphia, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - MLA, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - MLA, New York, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Modernized texts, principles, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Monthly expense file, May 18, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Dame Alice More, Lord Methsen, Holbein portrait, December 13, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - More, Book of Hours, copies of prayer, 1535 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - More, Book of Hours, negatives and prints, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - More, Book of Hours, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - More, Book of Hours, T.P. Grange, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Book of Hours, press release, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - More, Book of Hours, New Haven Register article, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - More and the Further I Goete, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Thomas More Association, Chicago, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - More, Coat of Arms, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - More, Coat of Arms, College of Arms, drawings and negatives, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Thomas More conference, Kenosha, lectures, February 7-28, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - More, engraving by R. Boissard, Bibliotheca, Chalcographica, 1650, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - More engraving, R. Woodman, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - More, French portrait, glossary print, February 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - More's head, where?, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Thomas More lectures, More House, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - More, letter to Cranevelt, signature, de Vocht, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - More, Medieval and Renaissance studies, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - More, letters, Ms. Royal D.XIV., folders 1-5, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - More, locale London, photos, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - More Medal, Kress Collection, National Gallery, Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - More, photos, bar convent portrait, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - More project, notice of in library staff news, March 1972 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - More and psychiatry, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - More, Thomas; readings (liturgical) for Feast, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - More, relics, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - More signature, 1514, doctor's commons, Lambeth, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - More statue, Chelsea; commemorative statue appeal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - More, trial and death, Knowles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - More and viking II, Plain of Utopia, September 1976 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Moreana, mailing list, revised to November 1971 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Morton's Fork, bridge, Undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Names, L and P, Undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - National portrait gallery, postcards, September 8, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - MLA, Neo-Latin, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Neo-Latin conference, MLA, Chicago, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Neo-Latin studies, Chicago; December 27, 1961; Room 8, 3:00-4:15 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Neo-Latin, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Neo-Latin, bibliographical aid, conferences, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Neo-Latin, international conference, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - New England Renaissance conference; Williams, April 13-14, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Newsletter, March 29, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Items for newsletter, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Newsletter, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Newsletter, October 1965 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Newsletter, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Newsletters, file copy, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Newsletter, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Newsletter, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Newsletter, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Newsletter, January 15, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Newsletter, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Newsletter, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Newsletter, June 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - O'Donnell on Salutati, from Fr. Cavanaugh, January 1961 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Old Spelling conference, York University, April 12-13, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Opinions, advisory committee, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Oxford University Press (N.Y.) Re: Cavendish, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Pace, Heywood, Yale Press, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Panofsky, Kenyon reviews, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Parker Society index, Erasmus, Fisher, Vergil, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Thomas Paynell, pages from commonplace book; St. John's College, Oxford, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Pentinger, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - R.S.S. personal file, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Carl H. Pforzheimer library catalogue, description of More items, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Piper, David; checklist of More portraits, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Photostat and microfilm bills, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Policy for grants, February 17, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Pottle, F., ventures article on Boswell project, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Press release, October 26, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Prévost thesis, notes on by R.S.S., Undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Vol. I (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Vol. III (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Vol. IV (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Vol. VI (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Vol. VII (popular), Undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Vol. VII (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Vol. VIII (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Vol. IX (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Vol. X (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Vol. XI (progress report), Undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Publication list, January 9, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Punctuation in 16th century, Undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Article on Rossens, Undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Reformation research, St. Louis, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Renaissance society, executive council, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Renaissance Society, London, May 29, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Report to adv. comm., May 1959 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Request for Quenes, newsletter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Responsis, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Review media, Gibson and Rogers, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Richard III, sample pages, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - CW 2, Rich. 3, new copy for third printing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Richard III, free copy list, Undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Analytic entries for Richard III, index, Undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Richard III, Bindoff, April 1961 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Rogers, free copy list, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Sample contracts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Sample texts and collations, poems, Undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Sample typescripts for editors (text), Undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - University of San Francisco Library, More collection, Undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Schoeck, 1956 report on Rogers' letters (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Schoeck, December 7, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Schoeck, talk on projects, November 1968 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Schoeck, legal bibliography, articles etc..., October 1, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Scholarly Series, 14 vol. format, June 1, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Sr. Scholastics, paper on More's sententia, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Erasmus in Utopien, circa 1930 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Secretary, research assistant, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Selected letters, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Selected letters, free copy list, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Selected letteres, revisions, paperback, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sloane 848, Picus summary, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sloane 1825, A Rueful Lamentation, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Style sheet, introduction, comm. etc..., November 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - London tablet, notice of project, October 24, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Tax ruling, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Temperus Filia Veritas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Times literary supplement, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Trinity, Cambridge Ms. More Genealogy, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Utopia, Encyclopedia Brittanica, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Utopia, specimens of Richards' transl., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Utopia translation, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Utopia, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Utopias not at Yale to 1750 (from Gibson 1-44), April 1, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Warburg, list of publications, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - West coast, March lecture tour, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Whitford, Pype of Perfection, notes on, March 20, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - University of Wisconsin Press, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Professional forum, March 27, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Yale corporation, December 6, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Yale press style sheet, February 1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Yale University, general information, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Report to advisory committee, May 1959 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Foley, Stephen; English 120 and 125 (parts 1 and 2), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
  - Sale reports, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Periodical list, RPM, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Personnel action forms, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hobertus, correspondence, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - More project, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Marc'hardour, correspondence, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Thomas More, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Orbitz, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Condolence letters, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Letters of tribute, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Millus, Donald, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Translation services, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - English 121-122, Text book orders (590B), 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Poisoned book, reader's comments, copy editing, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Poisoned book, text correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Poisoned book, vol. II, miscellaneous correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Keynote address, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Shanahan, July 21, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Rutter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Stringer, September 26, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Corres Yale press, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Barber, Nicolas, 1969-1979 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Latin poetry, illustrations, correspondence and business, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Latin poetry, notes on galleys and page project, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Latin poetry, copy editing and IJsewijn., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Project sketch for provost, Judith Hackman, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Hanna, 1968, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Hardison, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - General Index (standardized references), Undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Kapotsy, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Lawler lectures, February 14-16, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Lusardi, James P., 1960-1978 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Martz "More, the Author", Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - University of Glasgow library, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Illustrations for CW, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Roper, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - RSS, Vita and bibliography, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Whall, Seligman, June 13, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Richardson, June 14, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Biscan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Braden, Gordon, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Bundy, July 11, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Collins, August 15, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Culler, June 25, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Evans, June 26, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Frechette, Roger, December 18, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Hackett, May 20, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Haupt, paperback, devotional writings, 1974-1980 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Haupt, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Hirsch, Richard S., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, September 15, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Larkin, July 22, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Mack, June 2, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Dick, John, July 5, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Elton, October 12, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Gasbarra, Shane Stuart, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Greenblatt, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Thomas More (photographs included), Undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Emery, Ruth; St. John's conference, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Expenses, St. John's, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Action and Contemplation, St. Thomas More, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Illustrations for DCH, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Thomas More, donations, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - More's Utopia, portraits, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Miller; More, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Current accounts, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Yale press royalties, miscellaneous correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Typewriter, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Amici, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Yale Course Improvement Form (YCIF), November 5, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 44560, NEH grant, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 75387, rebate, NEH, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 44976, NEH grant, extension to, October 1977 - September 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 44857, NEH grant, extension to, September 1975 - December 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Book orders, inactive, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - NEH grant and extension, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 22830-75-604, NEH grant and extension, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - RE26982-77-1361, NEH grant and extension, rebate on grant, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Office supplies, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 74575, gifts for current use, July 1965 - June 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Memo of gifts file, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Appeals gifts receipts, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - More, royalty statements, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Book orders, current, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Da Lorenzo Valla a Tommaso Moro, Lo Statuto Umanistico della Teologia, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - De Tristitia, Valencia MS, copy flow, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Luncheon, deposits, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon, December 3rd; Elton, guest lecturer, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous contributors and friends, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Postage, receipts, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Luncheon, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Contributions receipts, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Library policy manual, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Office supplies, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon mailing master, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Office supplies, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Payroll distribution forms, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Payroll distribution forms, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Payroll, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photographic receipts, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - CHM's moving expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Postage records, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Printing statement, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Stationary and printing, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Telephone, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 74575, NEH, gifts for current use, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NEH, press, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General appropriations, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Old, possible support feelers, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bills (paid), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Check requests, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Personnel, tax benefits, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NEH reports, September 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Pay raises, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Final narrative report, NEH, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Matching for 1979-1981 grant (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - NEH grant, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 44757, NEH grant, June 1973 - August 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Reviews, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Extensions of grant, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Yale University library chart of accounts, July 1, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Yale press contract, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Inter-office correspondence and requests for contributions, 1978, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - NEH proposal, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - NEH, revised application, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Personnel activity repertory, L. Volpi, May 12, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, invoice, and stubs, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, invoice, stubs, etc..., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - ACLS and Guggenheim, 1963, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - NEH grant, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - NEH proposal, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Application, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Financials, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Financial reports, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Yale visiting housing, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 44684, NEH grant, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - NEH, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Illustrations for Responsio Ad Lutherum, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Early plans for project, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - More project, early prospectus, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Letters to prospective members of advisory committee, October 1958 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Formal announcement of project to advisory committee members, October 20, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - New England renaissance conference, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - New England renaissance conference, April 1965 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - New England renaissance conference, M.I.T., April 29-30, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Renaissance; Windsor, Canada, May 13-14, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - English institute, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - English institute, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - English institute, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - English institute, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - English institute, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - English institute, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - English institute, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - English institute, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon invitations, November 7, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Luncheon, October 22, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Luncheon, December 9, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter, May 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, June 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter, May 22, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Luncheon, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Luncheon, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Luncheon, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Luncheon, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Luncheon replies, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon replies, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Luncheon invitations, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Luncheon, December 6, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Luncheon, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Luncheon, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Luncheon list and replies, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Luncheon, December 1, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon and lecture, December 7, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon, December 6, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Annual luncheon, December 4, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Marc'hadour, 1971, May 1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Marc'hardour, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Markle, James A., Attorney, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Schultz, Nayda M., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Schütt, Marie, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Schweitzer, Ed., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Schweitzer, Ted, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Seofield party, May 20, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Schafer, John C., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 38)